I can't believe it...
Egoistic
Poriomania
I can't believe that this is the future that awaits me.
It's me. The Organization's interfering with events again.
What?!
Are you saying it's all the choice of Steins Gate?
I see.
I was careless.
Back when it all began, two weeks ago...
How could I have missed it?
Yeah, I know.
I'll call you again if I survive.
El. Psy. Kongroo.
Two weeks ago
Hello~
What's with that Hawaiian style, Daru?
It's not Hawaiian. It's LA.
LA?
What do you mean?
He mentioned it before.
Faris was invited to participate in a Rai-Net battle in America, so she invited us along.
Basically, the federal government wants the power of the great Hououin Kyouma on its side!
Wild delusions, fail as usual.
Ah, it's a message from Kurisu.
She says that the research she's working on is almost done, so she can come along!
It seems like she wants you to come too, Okarin.
Look.
Let's see.
"Okabe doesn't have to come though. It's not like I want to see him or anything."
She's a true tsundere. I get it.
The Future Gadget Laboratory could definitely use a foothold for global expansion!
Okarin's a tsundere too, isn't he?
America? Don't bother coming back.
Bring me something back!
What would you like, Moeka?
From: Shin
Macadamia
nuts x6
...anything but that.
Moeka
Some sweets would be sweet.
That must be them.
What's the purpose?
Normally, I would need to keep this secret...
I am mad scientist!
United States. Chaos and invade!
Mad scientist?
I'm a small citizen. Do you understand?
Do you understand? Do you understand?
Kyouma...
To think the Organization would join forces with the federal government in a bid to stop me...
I see you haven't changed, Okabe.
Okarin?
It's Kurisu.
Oh! I thought it was my
experiment-loving assistant, Christina.
I'm not your assistant!
I thought you may have been an agent of the Organization.
He's a walking failure. I have to do something...
Wild delusions, fail as usual.
Shut up!
Quit blabbering. Let's get going already.
Wait a second.
Don't tell me you're driving?
Have a problem with that?
Lukako...
Yes?
Go call a taxi.
Huh? Hey!
Why are you so out of breath?
What?
For the taxi fare.
Why should I?
You—
Kyouma!
Faris!
Why'd you cancel the hotel I booked?
We couldn't let the Organization know about our plans.
No way, is it the Seven Kings of North America?
Yeah. The Seven's Philosophy.
A Japan vs. America battle already?
Indeed.
But we must avoid pointless conflicts.
It'll be okay.
If I must, I will use the secret Desert Night!
Are you telling me you've already mastered it?!
The time has come! A distant 8770 kilometers from home, I announce it!
Until my body breaks and my soul passes on to Valhalla,
I shall fight valiantly in the Ragnarok!
I see you have quite the nice room for an assistant.
You guys can stay here until you find somewhere else.
Don't just do as you please!
Don't just drink what you please!
She's asleep!
I feel like I've seen this scene before.
This really is the most relaxing.
Just how much do you love labs?
How's life over here?
Nothing has really changed.
You didn't end up writing any
papers on time machines, right?
Ah, you mentioned something before about a different worldline.
It seems there might be others who have
memories of other worldlines, just like me.
You don't have to worry.
I only remember you saving me at Radio Kaikan, and then trying to find you to thank you.
Just that.
Are you sure that's all you remember?
Of course.
I see.
Hello?
Oh, you found something?
T-This is...
It's a motel!
Later then.
Wait!
You're going to just leave us here?!
You've got no choice. With your budget, motels are the only option.
Motels are where aliens take over people's bodies!
And they're where hockey-masked lunatics butcher people!
Don't confuse reality and fiction.
Too late for that now.
It's true that you see those kind of things in the movies, but it's still scary.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
It would be too much for Mayuri and Urushibara alone.
I'd be fine staying with Okarin. We used to sleep together often when we were kids.
Together?
What are you imagining?
Didn't you hear her say it was when we were kids?
Have some shame.
Shut it.
Either way, the girls and guys shouldn't share a room.
So, Urushibara—
You're a guy, aren't you?
Yes...
Oh well, I'll stay here with you all.
Okabe and Hashida are together. I'll stay with Mayuri.
Eh? I have to stay all by myself? It's scary...
Then Hashida can stay alone, and I'll stay with Mayuri.
That leaves Okabe and—
I don't mind, if it's with Kyouma.
But, he's a guy.
So, in the end, Makise ended up alone.
Well, there's no problem with Lukako and Mayuri staying together.
Lesbianism is in the air. Ha ha.
Don't even imagine it.
And if it's lesbian in the other room, then this room is—
Quit it!
Hey, Okarin.
What is it?
Let's decide with rock-paper-scissors which one of us sleeps in the car.
What's wrong?
I let him have my sleeping place.
The Supah Hakah is my important right-hand man, you see.
So you lost in rock-paper-scissors.
And why are you still up?
Just thinking a little.
Hey...
Won't you come in? Just for a little while.
I want to ask you about a few things.
Oh, this is Diet Dr Pepper!
Bring some home as souvenirs.
With the current exchange rate, it's cheaper here.
So, what did you want to ask me?
Is it about the Organization? Or perhaps...
If you're going to joke, just leave.
I've heard you say that before...
Before?
Another story, another worldline. Don't mind it.
That's what I wanted to ask about.
To be honest, I'm not all that sure about your theory of worldlines.
But just as you said, I've dreamed of things I haven't experienced.
For example, I had a dream where I was trying to cheer you up on a bridge in Akihabara.
I've dreamed about using the whiteboard while trying hard to explain something.
I've dreamed about fixing your lab coat in some dark place.
It's as I thought. You still have some of your memories.
So those were real?
Whether they're real or not is hard to explain.
They may as well be dreams to you in this worldline.
But they really happened in some other worldlines?
Yeah.
I see.
In that case, I have another question...
What is it?
Well...
I had another... weird dream.
One where you and I...
Well...
Well, what?
We...
What's wrong?
Do you need to go to the bathroom?
You pervert!
Okarin and Kurisu sure do get along well.
This decides it!
It's a virus card! Faris wins!
I won!
Faris! Faris! Faris!
A male beauty on stage!
He's a hit!
Sorry for the wait.
Wait just a minute.
Where's the "Nyan Nyan"?
Why do I have to do that?
Assistant, you're supposed to be a Japanese maid in America spreading our glorious culture!
I don't remember anyone saying anything about that!
And I don't want to do that either!
We agreed to work here to pay for the plane tickets.
It's only natural for a lab mem to help out.
I don't recall having someone else pay for my ticket.
Lab mems are one soul, one body.
Then why don't you do it too?!
If you have so much energy,
I guess you slept well last night.
It seemed like something was bothering you.
I was just a bit curious.
Well, that's not really it either.
Then just forget about it.
Nothing good can come out of
remembering other worldlines.
I know that.
I'd planned to forget it all.
I see.
Sorry for the wait!
Suzuha?
Suzuha!
Why is Suzuha here?
The last thing she said to me was...
"Thank you. I'll see you in seven years."
The time machine hasn't been invented in this world.
She can't exist here until she's born in seven years.
And yet, she's here.
Is there a time machine in this worldline too?
If that's true, it may mean World War III.
Huh? Okabe is gone?
He seemed to be in a panic,
and then I saw him go outside and leave.
Everyone!
I just heard that someone looking like him got in a taxi.
Really? I wonder if something happened.
It's just the usual.
Kurisu!
So that's why you followed me here.
That means you aren't her?
Yeah.
I just entered the Rai-Net tournament and am going to Las Vegas with my friends who live here.
Oh...
But, for you to follow me all the way here,
she must be really important to you.
This girl I look like.
Yeah, she is.
She's a precious friend.
You don't know where she is now?
She's not here.
But, I'll see her again in seven years. Definitely.
That's quite the wonderful story.
A fortune teller told me that I'll get
married and have a kid in seven years.
What is it?
It's nothing.
Sorry for taking up your time.
Don't worry about it. I had fun.
See you.
Yeah.
Seven years from now...
Of course she wouldn't know what I was talking about...
$0.67 left. The battery's dead too.
How am I supposed to get back?!
That was how it all started, two hours ago.
Kurisu...
Dammit! I can't let it end here!
I'm the mad scientist, Hououin Kyouma!
Not in a place like this...
I haven't even been able to tell her properly.
What are you talking about?
An illusion?
I am the reality as your brain interprets it
from the signals sent through your retinas.
I finally found you.
If you're going to come searching for me,
then at least check the gas before you leave.
I couldn't help it!
I was in a hurry.
What about your cell phone?
You're such a mess.
Your phone battery's dead,
you have a total of 67 cents,
and you were about to die lying face down in the middle of the highway!
I don't want to hear it from you!
It was unavoidable.
I thought I had seen an old friend.
An old friend?
That's it?
So it wasn't anything I needed to worry about.
Yeah.
Huh? What are you talking about?
That I'd forget it all.
It's about that?
Don't act like it's nothing!
It's very important to me!
Important?
Like I said... It's...
Remember how I said I had another weird dream?
I can't forget about it.
It's too realistic to be just a dream.
It's real.
Huh?
I said, it's real. To me, at least.
What do you mean?
I told you that I loved you in another worldline.
No, that's not it.
I love you.
What about you?
That's unfair.
We may have spent a lot of time together in another worldline,
but those times are all dreams to me in this worldline.
So... it's very confusing for me.
I possess the Reading Steiner, so I remember everything from the other worldlines.
That's why I know.
The three weeks I spent with you...
No, it was a much, much longer time.
I know because I was with you all along.
In any worldline, any time, any place, I love you.
I'll say it properly.
Makise Kurisu, I love you.
What about you?
Here and now, how do you feel about me?
I...
Do you want to know?
Close your eyes.
MUWAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA
Even the billions of heartbeats in the world
are nothing to you but insignificant
Whether we’re trapped in the past or lamenting over the future
predetermination does not allow even the slightest mistake
The infinite dreams and futures before us
are but vain privileges allowed to us
Finitude is what both clock hands show
toward a cruel destiny and choice
Hacking to the Gate
So now I cross worldlines every second
because I want to protect that smile of yours
And so, a time loop without sadness will once again
engulf me, the lone observer
So now I cross worldlines every second
because I want to protect that smile of yours
And so, a time loop without sadness will once again
engulf me, the lone observer